https://www.irvansmith.com/scart/privacy.php

Racing & Metal
Fabrication Equipment
Call Today:
800-221-7223
My Account | Cart Contents: 0 item(s)
All Products
All Brands Blowout Specials!Carts & WagonsCartsWagonsCleanersFasteners1/4 Turn Cam FastenersClecosGussetsHood Pins & AccessoriesNutplatesPanel FastenersPanel Fastener ButtonsAllen Steel ButtonsAluminum ButtonsSelf-Eject Steel ButtonsSlotted Steel ButtonsWinged Steel ButtonsPanel Fastener SpringsPanel Fastener StudPanel Fastener ToolsPanel Fastener Weld-On PlatesRivet Nutter Tool KitsRivets & Accessories1/8" Rivets3/16" RivetsBackup WashersColored RivetsCountersink RivetsDrill BitsLarge Secondary Head/Split RivetMultiGrip RivetsRivet GunsLongacre Racing ProductsAir TanksSet-Up ToolsBattery AccessoriesChassis SetupA-Arm ShimsAlignment EquipmentCaster Camber Gauges & AdaptersChassis Height GaugesClipboards, Sheets & ChecklistsPolyurathane Spring RubbersSet-Up ToolsShock Inflator SystemStagger & Tire TapesGauges and Dash PanelsAccutech Replacement GaugesAutometer Gauge PanelsBrake AccessoriesBrake AccessoriesBrake Balance Panels & KitsBrake FittingsBrake LinesElectrical ProductsGagelite Warning KitsGauge FittingsGauge LinesIndividual SendersLongacre Panels w/Accutech GaugeSwitch PanelsSwitches & AccessoriesTachometersInsulation and Heat ProtectionFirebraid SleevingHeader TapeHeat Protection & MatsPit Gloves & Heat SleeveRoll Bar PaddingMirrorsRear View Mirror KitsReplacement Mirrors and BracketsSpot Mirror KitsMiscellaneous ToolsAlignment EquipmentOil Filter CutterPit Guns & AccessoriesSet-Up ToolsShock Inflator SystemStagger & Tire TapesTesting EquipmentWrenches & Safety WirePit EquipmentAir Density & Spark Plug LightAir TanksAlignment EquipmentCanopiesCar Covers & Track MatsCaster Camber Gauges & AdaptersChassis Height GaugesClipboards, Sheets, & ChecklistsHeat Protection & MatsPit Gloves & Heat SleevePit Guns & AccessoriesSet-Up ToolsStagger & Tire TapesStopwatchesStorage CasesPyrometersInfra Red PyrometersProbe & Memory PyrometersSet-Up ToolsRace Car AccessoriesBattery AccessoriesBrake AccessoriesCar Covers & Track MatComputerscalesComputerscales - KartingDrink Holders & Radio BoxesHelmet HooksHood Pins & AccessoriesHot Lap In Car Systems & PartsHydraulic Clutch Line KitsPenske Shock BracketsRadiator CapsRear End Breathers & KitsRear View Mirror KitsReplacement Mirrors and BracketsRoll Bar PaddingScale LevelingScale StorageSet-Up ToolsShifter AccessoriesShock Inflator SystemSpoiler & Body SupportsSpot Mirror KitsStagger & Tire TapesSteering Wheel AccessoriesSteering WheelsTesting EquipmentThrottle Stops, Drains & BoltsWindshield CleanerWire TiesRivets & Rivet ToolsScales and AccessoriesAluminum Ramp SystemsComputerscalesComputerscales - KartingScale LevelingScale StorageSet-Up ToolsSwitches and Switch PanelsAdel ClampsBattery AccessoriesElectical ProductsGagelite Warning KitsIndividual SendersLongacre Panels w/Accutech GaugeSwitch PanelsSwitches & AccessoriesTachometersWeather Pack Wiring & Access.Timing ProductsStopwatchesStorage CasesTire Pressure GaugesDigital Tire Pressure GaugesSet-Up ToolsTire ToolsDigital Tire Pressure GaugesDurometers & Tire CareInfra Red PyrometersPit Guns & AccessoriesProbe & Memory PyrometersSet-Up ToolsSockets & HardwareStagger & Tire TapesTireliefs & AccessoriesOdds & EndsApparelBooks and VideosPocket KnivesPit EquipmentBump Steer GaugesCaster/Camber GaugesEngine LiftsFuel Transfer PumpsLevelsLongacre Pit EquipmentAir Density & Spark Plug LightsAir TanksAlignment EquipmentCar Covers & Track MatsCaster Camber Gauges & AdaptersChassis Height GaugesClipboards, Sheets, & ChecklistsHeat Protection & MatsPit Gloves & Heat SleevePit Guns & AccessoriesSet-Up ToolsStagger & Tire TapesStopwatchesStorage CasesPit Wagons & CartsBrakesCastersDo-It-Yourself KitsDump Can RacksGas Can CartsLatches & HandlesLista Cabinet/ToolboxLista Plastic BoxesPit CartsPit WagonsTire CartsTire RacksTires & WheelsPop-Up CanopiesCanopies and AccessoriesCanopy Replacement PartsRace JacksRacing ElectronicsRatchet Straps and Acc.AccessoriesAnchor Plate KitsCanopy ComponentsD Rings and Deck HardwareDragster PackagesE-Track & FittingsMac's Package DealsMac's Pro PacksMac's Super PacksMac's Ultra PacksMotorcycle Package DealsSuperClampTie Down StrapsTowing HardwareVersaTie ConnectorsVersaTie Track KitsVersaTie TracksWheel NetsRide Height GaugesSafety WireScalesSpring TestersTapeTiming EquipmentClipboardsStopwatchesTire ToolsDurometersTemp Gauges/PyrometersTire Bead BreakerTire Gauges & Air TanksTire MarkersTire Relief ValvesToe Plates and GaugesWrenches - LinePop-Up CanopiesCanopies and AccessoriesCanopy Replacement PartsRace Car PartsBrake FluidCar CoversCar PartsRod EndsGeneral PurposeHigh PerformanceHigh Performance-HDHigh Strength AlloyJam NutsPrecisionSteering Shaft SupportRotex Punch & AccessoriesRotex Punches and DiesServicesSoftwareSouvenirs-Ernie IrvanStorage SolutionsLista CabinetsPit Wagons & CartsCastersDo-It-Yourself KitsDump Can RacksGas Can CartsLatches & HandlesLista Cabinet/ToolboxPit CartsPit WagonsTire CartsTire RackTires & WheelsTires & WheelsTire Tools & EquipmentTires, Tubes & AssembliesWheels & Wheel CoversTools & EquipmentAccessoriesAir CompressorsBead RollersMandrelsISI MandrelsMittler Brothers MandrelsSpecialty Roll SetsBraided Hose CutterChassis JigsCNC MachineryDeburring ToolsDial IndicatorsDolliesDrill PressesEnglish WheelsEnglish Wheel AnvilsMittler Brothers English WheelsHole CuttersLathesMaterial TestersMillsMiscellaneousNibblersNotchersSheet Metal NotchersTubing NotchersNovakon MillsPipemaster ToolsPlanishing HammersPlate ShearPower ShearsPunchesBench PunchesMittler Brother Bench PunchesMittler Brother Bench Press ToolingRoper Whitney Bench PunchesHand PunchesHole FlaresHole PunchesKnockout PunchesLouver PunchesPunch/Flare CombosRotex PunchQuarter Midget ToolsSand BlastersBlast MediaBlast-It-All CabinetsSanders/GrindersSawsBand SawsBladesSawzall Saw BladesCold SawsEllis Parts & AccessoriesEllis Band Saw AccessoriesEllis Band Saw BladesEllis Band SawsEllis Belt Grinder and AccessoriesSheet Metal BrakesAccessoriesBox & PanMittler Brother Box & Pan Brake FingersHand BrakesPlate BrakesRadiusSpecialtyStraightSheet Metal RollersSheet Metal ShearsShrinker/StretchersMittler Brothers Shrinker/StretchersTaps & DiesTin/Aviation SnipsTransfer PunchesTubing BendersBendersShoe Sets-Hy-BendShoe Sets-ISIShoe Sets-ManualShoe Sets-Mittler180 Deg Manual Shoe Sets90 Deg Hydraulic Bender Shoe SetsShoe Sets-TubeSharkSoftwareUnibitsUsed Equipment
Log In
E-Mail Address:
Password:
Secure Log In
Password Forgotten?
Recently Viewed
Manufacturer
Please Select1/4 Turn FastenerAccucutterAuroraAutoHardwareBaileigh IndustrialBendTechBeverlyBlast-It-AllBluebirdBoyd-BuiltBrown ToolBrunnhoelzlBurr KingCarey MachineClecoCoolDraftEckoldEllisEncoErcolinaF.O.D. Control GroupFournier Enterprises, Inc..GeneralGracoGraingerGreenleeGrob, Inc.HossfeldHougenHy-BendImperial ToolIngersoll-RandIrvan-Smith, IncISCJetJoe's Racing ProductsKat'sKettKlein ToolsKlenkKMTListaLongacreM&RMac's Tie-DownsMalcoMarsonMartin WheelMerrick Machine Co.Metal AceMilbarMittler Bros. Machine and..NationalNational DetroitNorStarNovakonNvirocleanOval ResearchPanelfastPhase IIPipemaster ToolsPOPProLineRacing ElectronicsRepublicRoper WhitneyRotexSawzallSimplexSouthCoSpartan ChemicalSPISteve-Leavitt RacingTennsmithTorchmateTubeSharkTurn-ProUni-HydroUni-JigUS JackVisual Optics, Inc.Williams LowbuckWilwood
What's New?
Ellis Compensating Spring Assemblly Replacement$54.00
Reviews
I purchased this kit new in 2006 and used it as the base fra ..
Bestsellers
01. Lista PB-5 3" X 3" X 2" Red Plastic Boxes02. Cleco Model-1-8 1/8" X 0-1/4" Grip03. Panelfast S6375 1-3/8" x .375" Height Gold Spring04. Lista PB-6 3" X 6" X 2" Red Plastic Boxes05. Southco C2-33-15 Trigger Latch Raised Push Button - Black06. Lista PB-24 2" X 4" X 2" Red Plastic Boxes07. Spartan Chemical SD-20 All Purpose Degreaser/Cleaner 18 oz Can08. Cleco 3-16 3/16" X 0-1/4" Grip09. Lista PB-8 3" X 6" X 3" Red Plastic Boxes10. Panelfast 8220 1-3/8" Lightweight Beveled Weld-On D-PLATE
ShopPrivacy Notice
Storefront
Back
Privacy Notice
Irvan-Smith knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Irvan-Smith, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does irvansmith.com Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Irvan-Smith. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us:
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
Automatic Information:
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Irvan-Smith. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Irvan-Smith if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
E-mail Communications:
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Irvan-Smith if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this by selecting unsubscribed in the newsletters menu.
Information from Other Sources:
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts for storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Irvan-Smith coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Does Irvan-Smith Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries Irvan-Smith controls and as described below.
Agents:
We sometimes employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Promotional Offers:
We send only information about our own products to our customers via our newsletter feature. If you do not wish to receive this type of information, choose the unsubscribe option in your account.
Protection of Irvan-Smith and Others:
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Irvan-Smith, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
With Your Consent:
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
What Information Can I Access?
Irvan-Smith gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.
What Choices Do I Have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Irvan-Smith features as Automatic login, and permanent shopping carts. You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "My Account" pages. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this in the newsletter menu.
Children
Irvan-Smith does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use irvansmith.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit Irvan-Smith, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of North Carolina. If you have any concern about privacy at Irvan-Smith, please send us a thorough description to info@irvansmith.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
Information You Give Us
You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; by providing employer, school, or other such information; participate in Discussion Boards; provide and rate Reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and phone number; other people; content of reviews and e-mails to us; and financial information, including Social Security and driver's license numbers.
Automatic Information
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for.
Customer Service
Contact Us Shipping & ReturnsFAQRequest A Catalog
My Account
LoginGeneral informationEdit account info.My address bookAccount historyProduct notificationsMy Wishlist
Company Info
About Us Map/Driving Directions Privacy Notice Conditions of Use
